Finding Aid for Esquire, Inc. Records 1933-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence with authors and agents
  - C (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - D (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - Frazier, George (Box 25)
  - F (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - Glinn, Burt (Box 25)
  - G (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - H (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - J (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - Klein, William (Box 25)
  - K (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - Lees, David (Box 25)
  - Littauer and Wilkinson (Box 25)
  - L (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - McIntyre, Alice (Box 25)
  - Mailer, Norman (Box 25)
  - Miller, Helen Hill (Box 25)
  - M (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - N-0 (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - O'Brien, Bob (Box 25)
  - Olmstead, Constance (Box 25)
  - P-R (Miscellaneous) (Box 25)
  - Reeves, Rosser (Box 25)
  - Samugheo, Chiara (Box 25)
  - Sanford, Jay (Box 25)
  - Schoenbrun, David (Box 25)
  - Schulberg, Ad (Box 25)
  - Schulberg, Budd (Box 25)
  - Slomka, Irving S. (Box 26)
  - Smith, Gabrielle (Box 26)
  - Sonnenberg, Ben (Box 26)
  - Spink, Taylor J.G. (Box 26)
  - Sterling Lord Agency (Box 26)
  - Steuer, Art (Box 26)
  - Strassman, Toni (Box 26)
  - Styron, William (Box 26)
  - S (Miscellaneous) (Box 26)
  - Tynan, Kenneth (Box 26)
  - T (Miscellaneous) (Box 26)
  - Vidal, Gore (Box 26)
  - Wechsberg, Joseph (Box 26)
  - Williams, Tennessee (Box 26)
  - Winocour, Jack (Box 26)
  - Wintle, A.D. (Box 26)
  - V-Z (Miscellaneous) (Box 26)
- Staff correspondence
  Staff Correspondence is a smaller series arranged alphabetically by name of staff member. The most significant files are those for Clay Felker.
  - Benton, Robert, 1961-1962 (Box 26)
  - Brower, Brock, 1960-1961 (Box 26)
  - Christgau, Robert, 1967 (Box 26)
  - Felker, Clay (Personal)
    - 1956-1961 General (Box 26)
    - 1958-1959 re. Rockefeller campaign (Box 26)
    - 1959-1960 re. Ford Motor Company (Box 26)
    - 1960-1961 re. Bill Vanden Heuvel campaign (Box 26)
    - 1961 re. Infinity (Box 26)
    - 1961-1962 re. Common Market book (Box 26)
    - 1961 re. Carl Felker (Box 26)
  - Felker, Clay (Inter-Office)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 26)
    - 1959 (Box 26)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 26)
- Assorted business files
  Assorted Business Files includes information about inventory, write-offs, routing of scripts, and other legal and financial miscellanea.
  - Manuscripts purchased, 1959-1960 (Box 26)
  - Inventory
    - 1953-1954 (Box 26)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 26)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 26)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 26)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 26)
  - Write-Offs
    - 1953-1960 (Box 26)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 26)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 26)
    - 1965 (Box 26)
  - Scripts Routing 1965-1966 (Box 26)
  - Requisition Record 1971 (Box 26)
  - Purchase Contracts 1965-1969 (Box 26)
  - Legal Review Record Book 1968-1970 (Box 26)
- Audio Recording
  [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
  - Recording of literary conversation between William Styron and James Jones, [Undated], Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 3 ¾ ips
    - [Part 1], [85177-SR-1-1]; mp3 file; (Discusses "The Confessions of Nat Turner" and Southern America, Slavery, and social strife of the time.)
Index to The Sound And The Fury series
Buckley, William Frank, 1925-
Sept. 12, 1962
Church, Frank, 1924-
Aug. 2, 1966
Heston, Charlton, 1923-
Jan. 26, 1966
Hopper, Hedda, 1890-1966.
Feb. 22, 1961
Lowry, Robert James, 1919-
Mar. 25, 1960
Miller, Arthur, 1915-
Feb. 13, 1967
Mondale, Walter Frederick, 1928-
June 4, 1969
Nabokov, Vladimir, 1899-
Apr. 9, 1965
O'Hair, Madalyn Murray
Nov. 11, 1964; Feb. 2, 1965
Porter, Katherine Anne, 1890-
Feb. 27, 1967
Powell, Adam Clayton, 1908-1972.
Mar. 10, 1968
Rabe, David William, 1940-
Aug. 3, 1968
Sheed, Wilfrid John Joseph, 1930-
Mar. 28, 1969
Thomas, Norman Mattoon, 1884-1968.
July 21, 1966
Thompson, Hunter S.
Oct. 8, 1959
Yorty, Samuel William, 1909-
Oct. 16, 1968
Index to Authors, Agents, and Staff Correspondence series
Brownmiller, Susan
Feb. 15, 1968
Condon, Richard, 1915-
Mar. 28, 1967
Felker, Clay S., 1928-
(10 folders)
Mailer, Norman, 1923-
June 8, 1962; Dec. 9, 1961; Nov. 10, 1959; Oct. 27, 1959; Oct. 8, 1959
Mauldin, William H., 1921-
Oct. 26, 1960 (cartoonists correspondence)
Schoenbrun, David Franz, 1915-
1958-1961 (1 folder)
Schulberg, Budd, 1914-
folder
Styron, William, 1925-
Aug. and Sept. 10, 1961
Wechsberg, Joseph, 1907-
folder